SANJANA KASHYAP

PROFILE SUMMARY

Human resources representative with 4 years of experience in managing employee benefits, employee hiring and onboarding, performance management and HR records. Reliable and organized team member with the ability to communicate effectively and handle office changes. Skilled at building and maintaining relationships, representing shared company values and managing employees across all levels of an organization. Proficient with HRIS and benefits management.

CONTECT

Contact No: +91 9998823745

Email:

Sanjana.kashyaap@gmail.com Address: Ahmedabad, Gujarat

WORK EXPERIENCE

Associate Human Resources, Oct 2022 to Present RBSA Advisor - Ahmedabad

- Responsible mainly for overall employee life cycle and business.
- Ensure recruitment as per the manpower plan and within budgets and timelines partnering with internal stakeholders.
- Handling day-to-day employee queries and grievances PAN India, Preparing various MIS reports, and sharing with the management on a monthly/quarterly/yearly basis.
- Supporting employee welfare and day-to-day functioning of the department.
- Handling HR operations like employee induction & orientation, joining formalities, Exit formalities, HRMS, and other HR-related communications, and initiatives PAN India.
- Issuance of various letters, ID & Visiting cards.
- Initiate various employee engagement activities, increase employee engagement across the organization.
- Maintain daily attendance data for the respective office/location, keep track of confirmation due dates, increment due dates, and the exit dates.
- Coordination with PAN Admin team and for implementation of various systems and processes support managing all statutory compliances
- Assist handling administrative tasks.

Talent Care Advisor, Jan 2022 to Sept 2022 IBM India Pvt Ltd - Bangalore

- Hosting in-house career days for students and recent graduates by department or field of expertise.
- Attending college career fairs, interacting with students, and promoting our employer's brand.
- Screening resumes, conducting interviews, and performing skills assessment tests for positions and internships.
- Report on recruiting metrics after every career event, including the number of candidates, interviewed and hired.

- Advertise current open roles.
- Contact university career counselors and provide informative materials about our internship and full-time job programs.
- Liaise with team leaders to define hiring needs and design internship programs.
- Build and maintain good relationships with universities and other educational institutions. Support to Onboarding Team (conducting online sessions for onboarding which includes Documents verification, Providing a brief description of company policies, Solving employee queries, etc.

Talent Acquisioin Specialist, Jan 2021 to Dec 2021 Teksun inc - Ahmedabad

- Responsible for end-to-end recruitment of both IT and Non-IT.
- Understanding manpower requisition from the concerned department.
- Sourcing candidates that match the desired skills.
- Posting job descriptions on JB boards and tracking, posting, and maintaining the results. Develop and update job descriptions.
- Screening the candidates by conducting telephonic interviews.
- Encouraging employees to provide references for better prospects.
- Communicating the employment status to applied candidates.
- Negotiate the current salary of the candidates and finalize them likewise.
- Utilized job boards, internal resources, referrals, and networking to recruit.
- Maintaining and updating the database of the candidates.
- Tie up with the Recruitment Consultancy.
- Coordination with the consultancy till the candidate joins.
- Support HR Manager in On boarding, Employee engagement activities, Database management also in Vendor management.

HR Cum Admin Executive, Jan 2020 to Dec 2020 Exopet India Pvt Ltd - Ahmedabad

- Involved in the end-to-end recruitment life cycle.
- Sourcing candidates from different job portals.
- Screen candidates' resumes, interview candidates, schedule interviews, and extend offers. Negotiate pay rates and salaries and other requirements that candidates have, and obtained commitment from candidates for current and future job requirements.
- Help candidates prepare for both Telephonic and in-person interviews and kept them in a loop with the latest updates from clients.
- Daily interaction with prospective candidates, coordination, scheduling, post offering follow-ups.
- Arranging onboarding sessions for all the new employees.
- Handling office tasks such as filing, generating reports and presentations, and setting up meetings.
- Making travel arrangements Greet and assist visitors.
- Maintain professional communication with clients and deal with their inquiries via Phone and Email.
- Courier management.
- Create and update records in the database.
- Maintain stock lists

Admin Executive , Oct 2018 to Dec 2019 Pam Technologies Pvt Ltd - Ahmedabad, India

- Coordination with the clients via mail or phone.
- Responsible for handling customer inquiries.
- Database management in excel.
- Sourcing Candidates from different job portals.
- Screening and Shortlisting relevant profiles and scheduling candidates for interviews Communicating with every candidate and creating a good sense of understanding with the candidate.
- Coordination and regular follow-up with candidates.
- Maintain checklists, trackers, reports, and follow-up status.
- Forming and maintaining employee records Attendance management.
- Develop recruitment form
- Responsible for the onboarding process

EDUCATION

PGDM, 2017

St. Kabir Institute Of Professional Studies -Ahmedabad

Percentage - 60%

Bachelor of Commerce, 2015

Gujarat University - Ahmedabad

Percentage - 60%

Intermediate (Class XII), Commerce, 2012

CBSE - Gandhinagar

CGPA/Percentage - 62%

Matriculation (Class X), 2010

CBSE - Gandhinagar

CGPA/Percentage - 6.8%

SKILLS

- Organization and Time Management.
- Proficient in office tools (Excel, PowerPoint, Word).
- Report Generation.
- Worked on tools –(Tracker, Leadsquared).
- Communication Skills

- Database Management.
- Spreadsheet Management.
- Service-focused.
- Complex Problem Solver.

INTERNSHIP

- Company: ONGC, Ahmadabad
- Topic: Detailed Study on Training and Development.
- Duration: 6 weeks
- Company: Star Union Dai-ichi Life Insurance, Ahmedabad.
- Topic: Detailed Study on Talent Acquisition.
- Duration: 45 day

DECLARATION

CTC - at last before declaration 4.70 LPA

"I hereby declare that all the entries are correct to the best of my knowledge. If chance is given to me, I assure you that, I will prove myself as an asset to your organization."